A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Special Studies Project, RG 4 FA387
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Studies Project, 1956-1964; 4; 28 Cubic Feet 70 boxes
  - Subpanel II: International Security Objectives and Strategy, 1956-1964; B
    - Papers - Gilpatric, Roswell - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Papers - Gilpatric, Roswell - Paper II-7 - "Notes on What Lies Ahead for the U.S. Defense Establishment", 1953-1963 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Papers- Bascom, Willard R. - Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Papers- Bascom, Willard R. - Paper II-8 - "Old Uses for a New Navy", 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Papers - Bascom, Willard R. - Paper II-10 - "To Be Or Not To Be", 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Papers - De Weerd, H. A. - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Papers - De Weerd, H. A. - Paper II-11 - "Trends and Problems in NATO", 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Papers - Teller, Edward - Paper II-12 - "The Nature of Nuclear War", 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Papers - Lincoln, George A. and Jordan, Amos A. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Papers - Lincoln, George A. and Jordan, Amos A. - Paper II-13 - "Technology and the Changing Nature of General War", 1956 (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Papers - Miles, Arnold - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Papers - Miles, Arnold - Paper II-14 - "Notes on Strengthening the Department of Defense", 1957 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1, 1956 November 29-30 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2, 1956 December 20 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3, 1957 January 24-25 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Papers, 1957 January 24-25 (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4, 1957 March 7-10 (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - Report Drafts - Hoopes, Townsend, 1957 May 3 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - Report Drafts - McCormack, James, 1957 April 22 - August 21 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Report Drafts - Lincoln, George, 1957 May (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 June 15 - 29 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight and McCormack, James, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 July 11-18 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 July 15, 28 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 August 1 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 August 7 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - Report Drafts - Cooke, Dwight, 1957 October 3 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 August 10 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 August 15 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry and McCormack, James, 1957 August 29 (Box 17, Folder 191)
    - Report Drafts - Coffey, J. I., 1957 December 1 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 December 3 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 December 4 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Report Drafts - Hoopes, Townsend, 1957 December 11 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 December 14 (Box 18, Folder 196)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry, 1957 December 24 (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry - Comments - Draft, December 27, 1957, 1957 December 27 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry - Comments - Draft, December 27, 1957, 1957 December 27 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry - Comments - Draft, December 27, 1957, 1957 December 27 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - Report Endorsements, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Report Draft - Summary, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Report - Summary, 1958 January 5 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - Report - Public Release Copy, 1958 January 5 (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - Report - Manuscript for Printer, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Report - Press Release, 1958 January 5 (Box 19, Folder 206)
    - Report - Printed Copy, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 207)
  - Subpanel III: International Economic and Social Objectives and Strategy, 1956-1964; C
    - Administration - Issue Summaries, 1956 November-December (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - Membership - Anderson, Robert B., 1956-1961 (Box 19, Folder 209)
    - Membership Files - Bowles, Chester, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 210)
    - Membership Files - Bowles, Chester, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - Membership - Cowles, John, 1956-1961 (Box 19, Folder 212)
    - Membership - Katz, Milton, Chairman, 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 213)
    - Membership - Katz, Milton, Chairman, 1957-1962 (Box 19, Folder 214)
    - Membership - Maffry, August, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 215)
    - Membership - May, Stacy, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - Membership - Murden, Forrest D., 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - Membership - Rockefeller, David, 1956-1962 (Box 20, Folder 218)
    - Papers - Organization, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 219)
    - Papers - Gordon, Lincoln - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 220)
    - Papers - Gordon, Lincoln - Paper III-1 - "Economic Aid and Trade Policy as an Instrument of National Strategy", 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 221)
    - Papers - Critz, Harry H. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 222)
    - Papers - Critz, Harry H. - Paper III-2 - "Mutual Security Objectives, Operations, and Trends of Military Aid", 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 223)
    - Papers - Killough, Hugh B. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 224)
    - Papers - Killough, Hugh B. - Paper III-4 - "Economic Implications and ...An Expanding World Trade", 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 225)
    - Papers - Schelling, Thomas C. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 226)
    - Papers - Schelling, Thomas C. - Paper III-5 - "American...Assistance and the Newly Independent Countries", 1956 (Box 20, Folder 227)
    - Papers - Cleveland, Harlan - Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    - Papers - Cleveland, Harlan - Paper III-6 - "The Theory and Practice of Foreign Aid", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 229)
    - Papers - Kulski, Wadyslaw W. - Correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 21, Folder 230)
    - Papers - Kulski, Wladsyslaw W. - Paper III-7 - "The Pattern of Soviet Policies Towards the Underdeveloped Countries", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 231)
    - Papers - Harbison, Frederick H. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 232)
    - Papers - Harbison, Frederick H. - Paper III-8 - "Labor Problems in Industrialization of Underdeveloped Countries", 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 233)
    - Papers - Levy, Walter J. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 234)
    - Papers - Levy, Walter J. - Paper III-10 - "The Suez Crisis...", 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 235)
    - Papers - Davis, Kingsley - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 236)
    - Papers - Davis, Kingsley - Paper III-11 - "World Population Trends and American Policy", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 237)
    - Papers - Coole, Ansley J. and Hoover, Edgar M. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 238)
    - Papers - Coole, Ansley J. and Hoover, Edgar M. - Paper III-12 - "Prospects for Economic Growth...", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 239)
    - Papers - Mosher, Arthur T. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 240)
    - Papers - Mosher, Arthur T. - Paper III-13 - "The Role of Agriculture in Underdeveloped Countries...", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 241)
    - Papers - Taeuber, Irene B. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 242)
    - Papers - Taeuber, Irene B. - Paper III-14 - "Demographic Difficulties...in Asia and North Africa", 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 243)
    - Meetings, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 244)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1, 1956 December 14 (Box 22, Folder 245)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2, 1957 January 16 (Box 22, Folder 246)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3, 1957 February 22 (Box 22, Folder 247)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4, 1958 March 14 (Box 22, Folder 248)
    - Report Drafts - General File, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 249)
    - Report Drafts - Murden, Forrest, 1957 April 23 (Box 22, Folder 250)
    - Report Drafts - Murden, Forrest, 1957 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 251)
    - Report Drafts - Coffey, James I., 1957 May 3-June 17 (Box 23, Folder 252)
    - Report Drafts - Coffey, James I., 1957 June 19 (Box 23, Folder 253)
    - Report Drafts - Katz, Milton, 1957 July 18 (Box 23, Folder 254)
    - Report Drafts - Hughes, Emmet J., 1957 August 27 (Box 23, Folder 255)
    - Report Drafts - Loth, 1957 September 18, October 9 (Box 23, Folder 256)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, Richard, 1958 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 257)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, Richard, 1958 February 21 (Box 23, Folder 258)
    - Report Drafts - Gardner, Richard and Heilbroner, Robert H., 1958 March 3 (Box 24, Folder 259)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert H., 1958 March 4 (Box 24, Folder 260)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 March 5 (Box 24, Folder 261)
    - Report Drafts - Comments, 1958 March 5 (Box 24, Folder 262)
    - Report Drafts - Katz, Milton, 1958 March 19 (Box 24, Folder 263)
    - Report Drafts - Berle, Adolf, 1958 May 14 (Box 24, Folder 264)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 May 14-15 (Box 24, Folder 265)
    - Report Drafts - May, Stacy, 1958 May 16 (Box 24, Folder 266)
    - Report Drafts - Authorship Not Attributed, 1958 May 16 (Box 24, Folder 267)
    - Report Drafts - Editorial Comments, 1958 May 16 (Box 24, Folder 268)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry and May, Stacy, 1958 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 269)
    - Report Drafts - Thornburg, Max, 1958 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 270)
    - Report Drafts - Authorship Not Attributed, 1958 May 29 (Box 25, Folder 271)
    - Report Drafts - Editorial Comments, 1958 May 29 (Box 25, Folder 272)
    - Report Drafts - Authorship Not Attributed, 1958 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 273)
    - Report Drafts - Editorial Comments, 1958 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 274)
    - Report Drafts - Authorship Not Attributed, 1958 June 7 (Box 25, Folder 275)
    - Report Correction, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 276)
    - Report Endorsements, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 277)
    - Report Press Release, 1958 June 15 (Box 25, Folder 278)
    - Report - Printed Copy, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 279)
    - Report - Public Release Copy, 1958 June 15 (Box 26, Folder 280)
    - Report Summary, 1958 June 15 (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - Subpanel IV: United States Economic and Social Policy, 1956-1964; D
    - Administration - Issue Summaries, 1956 October-November (Box 26, Folder 282)
    - Membership - Burns, Arthur F., 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 283)
    - Membership - Butler, William F., 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 284)
    - Membership - Granger, Lester B., 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 285)
    - Membership - Josephs, Devereux C., 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 286)
    - Membership - Livingston, Joseph A., 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 287)
    - Membership - Manning, Bayless, 1956-1961 (Box 26, Folder 288)
    - Membership - McCabe, Thomas B., 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 289)
    - Membership - Perkins, Roswell B., 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 290)
    - Membership - Riefler, Winfield, 1956-1958 (Box 27, Folder 291)
    - Membership - Rosenberg, Anna M., 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 292)
    - Membership - Rostow, Eugene V., 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 293)
    - Membership - Thomson, J. Cameron, 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 294)
    - Membership - Wilde, Frazar B., 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 295)
    - Membership - Wilde, Frazar B., 1959-1963 (Box 27, Folder 296)
    - Papers - Organization, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 297)
    - Papers - Keezer, Dexter M. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 298)
    - Papers - Keezer, Dexter M. - Paper IV-1 - "Government Responsible for Economic Growth", 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 299)
    - Papers - Colm, Gerhard - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 300)
    - Papers - Colm, Gerhard - Paper IV-2 - "America at the Threshold of Abundance", 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 301)
    - Papers - Ensley, Grover W., 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 302)
    - Papers - Ensley, Grover W. - Paper IV-3 - "The Hopes and Prospects for Economic Growth", 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 303)
    - Papers - Fellner, William J. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 304)
    - Papers - Fellner, William J. - Paper IV-4 - "Long-Run Problems of Fiscal Policy", 1956 (Box 28, Folder 305)
    - Papers- Musgrave, Richard A. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 306)
    - Papers- Musgrave, Richard A. - Paper IV-5 - "The Outlook for Federal Tax Policy", 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 307)
    - Papers - Somers, Herman M. and Anne R. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 308)
    - Papers - Somers, Herman M. and Anne R. - Paper IV-6 - "Social Insurance in the U.S.", 1957 (Box 28, Folder 309)
    - Papers - Dahl, Robert A. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 310)
    - Papers - Dahl, Robert A. - Paper IV-7 - "The Role of Government in Individual and Social Welfare", 1956-1958 (Box 29, Folder 311)
    - Papers - Paper IV-8 - "Individual and Social Welfare", 1956 (Box 29, Folder 312)
    - Papers - Schultz, Theodore W. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 313)
    - Papers - Paper IV-9 - "A Working Paper on Agriculture", 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 314)
    - Papers - Efferson, J. Norman - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 315)
    - Papers - Efferson, J. Norman - Paper IV-10 - "Some Concepts and Long-Time Objectives of Agricultural Policy", 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 316)
    - Papers - Fisher, Joseph L. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 317)
    - Papers - Fisher, Joseph L. - Paper IV-12 - "The Outlook for Natural Resources", 1957 (Box 29, Folder 318)
    - Papers - Lindsay, Franklin A. - Paper IV-13 - "Planning for Non-Renewable Resources", 1957 (Box 29, Folder 319)
    - Papers - Lindsay, Franklin A. - Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 29, Folder 320)
    - Papers - Osborn, Fairfield and Snider, Robert G. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 321)
    - Papers - Osborn, Fairfield and Snider, Robert G. - Paper IV-14 - "Statement on U.S. Water Problems", 1957 (Box 29, Folder 322)
    - Papers - Williams, Ernest - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 29, Folder 323)
    - Papers - Williams, Ernest - Paper IV-15 - "Transportation: Trends, Problems and Recommendations", 1957 (Box 29, Folder 324)
    - Papers - Grodzins, Morton - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 30, Folder 325)
    - Papers - Grodzins, Morton - Paper IV-16 - "The Metropolitan Area as a Racial Problem", 1957 (Box 30, Folder 326)
    - Papers - Woodbury, Coleman - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 30, Folder 327)
    - Papers - Woodbury, Coleman - Paper IV-17 - "Policy Concepts in Housing", 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 328)
    - Papers - Cohen, Wilbur - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 30, Folder 329)
    - Papers - Cohen, Wilbur - Paper IV-18 - "Social Policies and Social Services in an Expanding Economy", 1957 (Box 30, Folder 330)
    - Papers - Newcomb, Robinson - Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 331)
    - Papers - Newcomb, Robinson - Paper IV-19 - "Housing Perspectives", 1957 (Box 30, Folder 332)
    - Meetings - Organization, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 333)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 January 3-4 (Box 30, Folder 334)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Transcript, 1957 January 3-4 (Box 30, Folder 335)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 336)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Transcript, 1957 February 8-9 (Box 30, Folder 337)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 March 11-12 (Box 31, Folder 338)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Transcript, 1957 March 11-12 (Box 31, Folder 339)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 April 16-17 (Box 31, Folder 340)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Material Distributed, 1957 April 16-17 (Box 31, Folder 341)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Transcript, 1957 April 16-17 (Box 31, Folder 342)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 5 - Organizational Records, Material Distributed, 1957 May 19 (Box 31, Folder 343)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 5 - Transcript, 1957 May 19 (Box 31, Folder 344)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 6 - Organizational Records, Transcripts (Partial), 1958 January 24 (Box 31, Folder 345)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 7 - Organizational Records, 1958 April 1 (Box 31, Folder 346)
    - Meetings - Drafting Committee - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, 1957 April 29 (Box 31, Folder 347)
    - Meetings - Drafting Committee - Meeting No. 2 - Organizational Records, Transcripts, 1957 June 7 (Box 31, Folder 348)
    - Meetings - Drafting Committee - Meeting No. 3 - Organizational Records, Transcripts, 1957 July 18 (Box 31, Folder 349)
    - Meetings - Executive Committee - Meetings Nos. 1-2 - Organizational Records, 1958 March 25, April 14 (Box 31, Folder 350)
    - Report Drafts - General Material, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 351)
    - Report Drafts - Manning, Bayless, 1957 April 12 (Box 32, Folder 352)
    - Report Drafts - Hoopes, Townsend, 1957 February 27- April 18 (Box 32, Folder 353)
    - Report Drafts - Draft, 1957 April 25 (Box 32, Folder 354)
    - Report Drafts - Draft, 1957 May 2 (Box 32, Folder 355)
    - Report Drafts - Report Summary, 1957 May 4 (Box 32, Folder 356)
    - Report Drafts - Draft, 1957 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 357)
    - Report Drafts (Outline) - Butler, William F., 1957 June 24 (Box 32, Folder 358)
    - Report Drafts - Manning, Bayless, 1957 May 15 (Box 32, Folder 359)
      As amended July 3, 1957
    - Report Drafts - Perkins, Roswell B., 1957 July 12 (Box 32, Folder 360)
    - Report Drafts - Butler, William F., 1957 July 18 (Box 32, Folder 361)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 August 13 (Box 33, Folder 362)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 August 27 (Box 33, Folder 363)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 September 9 (Box 33, Folder 364)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert, 1957 November 7 (Box 33, Folder 365)
    - Report Drafts - Draft Mock-up, 1957 November 11 (Box 33, Folder 366)
    - Report Drafts - Draft, 1957 December 19 (Box 33, Folder 367)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 January 16 (Box 33, Folder 368)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 January 18 (Box 33, Folder 369)
    - Report Drafts - Granger, Lester, 1958 January 31 (Box 33, Folder 370)
    - Report Drafts - Berle, Adolf, 1958 February 25 (Box 33, Folder 371)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 January 31 (Box 34, Folder 372)
    - Report Drafts - Dean, Gordon, 1958 February 25 (Box 34, Folder 373)
    - Report Drafts - May, Stacy, 1958 February 26 (Box 34, Folder 374)
    - Report Drafts - Draft Outline, 1958 March 12 (Box 34, Folder 375)
    - Report Drafts - Stein, 1958 March 12 (Box 34, Folder 376)
    - Report Drafts - Perkins, Roswell B., 1958 March 19 (Box 34, Folder 377)
    - Report Drafts - Stein, 1958 March 20 (Box 34, Folder 378)
    - Report Drafts - May, Stacy, 1958 March 25 (Box 34, Folder 379)
    - Report Drafts - Draft - March 30, 1958 - Comments Compiled, 1958 March 30 (Box 34, Folder 380)
    - Report Drafts - Draft - April 3, 1958 - Comments Compiled, 1958 April 3 (Box 34, Folder 381)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A. - Draft (April 4, 1958) - Comments Compiled, 1958 April 4 (Box 34, Folder 382)
    - Report Drafts - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1958 April 8 (Box 35, Folder 383)
    - Report Drafts - Heilbroner, Robert - Comments - April 8, 1958, 1958 April 8 (Box 35, Folder 384)
    - Report Drafts - Draft - April 10, 1958 - Comments, 1958 April 10 (Box 35, Folder 385)
    - Report Drafts - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 April 15 (Box 35, Folder 386)
    - Report Drafts - Summary and Excerpts, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 387)
    - Report Endorsements, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 388)
    - Report - Public Release Copy, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 389)
    - Report - Press Release, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 390)
    - Report - Printed Copy, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 391)
    - Report - Summary and Excerpts, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 392)
  - Subpanel V: United States Utilization of Human Resources, 1956-1964; E
    - Administration - Authors and Issues Outlines, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 393)
    - Organization - Participants, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 394)
    - Membership - Gardner, John W. (Chairman), 1955-1958 (Box 36, Folder 395)
    - Membership - Gardner, John W. (Chairman), 1961 (Box 36, Folder 396)
    - Membership - Haskins, Caryl P., 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 397)
    - Membership - Hechinger, Fred M., 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 398)
    - Membership - Hesburgh, Father Theodore M., 1956-1962 (Box 36, Folder 399)
    - Membership - Hickey, Margaret, 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 400)
    - Membership - Killian, James R., 1956-1962 (Box 37, Folder 401)
    - Membership - Riesman, David, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 402)
    - Membership - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 403)
    - Membership - Wilson, Howard E., 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 404)
    - Membership - Wolfe, Dael, 1956-1967 (Box 37, Folder 405)
    - Papers - Kirk, Dudley - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 406)
    - Papers, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 407)
    - Papers - Kirk, Dudley - Paper V-1 - "Prospective Population Growth...", 1956 (Box 37, Folder 408)
    - Papers - Brown, J. Douglas - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 409)
    - Papers - Brown, J. Douglas - Paper V-2 - "High Talent Manpower for Science and Manpower", 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 410)
    - Papers - Coombs, Philip H. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 411)
    - Papers - Coombs, Philip H. - Paper V-3 - "The Challenge of American Education's New Era", 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 412)
    - Papers - Ginzberg, Eli, 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 413)
    - Papers - Ginzberg, Eli - Paper V-4a - "Human Resources and National Policy", 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 414)
    - Papers - Lindsay, Franklin A. - Paper V-5 - "The Supply of Creative and Skilled Manpower", 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 415)
    - Papers - Coggeshall, Lowell T. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 38, Folder 416)
    - Papers - Coggeshall, Lowell T. - Paper V-6 - "National Health - Socialogical Aspects", 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 417)
    - Papers - Whitehorn, John C. - Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 38, Folder 418)
    - Papers - Whitehorn, John C. - Paper V-7 - "Social Psychiatry - Working Concepts", 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 419)
    - Papers - Straus, Donald B. - Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box 38, Folder 420)
    - Papers - Straus, Donald B. - Paper V-8 - "Developing a National Policy on ... Physicians' Services", 1957 (Box 38, Folder 421)
    - Papers - Farnsworth, Dana L. - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 38, Folder 422)
    - Papers - Farnsworth, Dana L. - Paper V-9 - "Social and Emotional Development of Students", 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 423)
    - Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 424)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 January 7 (Box 38, Folder 425)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 1 - Transcript, 1957 January 7 (Box 38, Folder 426)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 February 10-11 (Box 38, Folder 427)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Transcript, 1957 February 10-11 (Box 38, Folder 428)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Papers, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 429)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 2 - Papers, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 430)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Organizational Records, Minutes, 1957 March 12-13 (Box 39, Folder 431)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 3 - Transcript, 1957 March 12-13 (Box 39, Folder 432)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Administrative Records, Minutes, 1957 April 11-12 (Box 39, Folder 433)
    - Meetings - Meeting No. 4 - Papers, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 434)